<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>m4dfry</title>
    <link>https://blog.m4dfry.space/</link>
    <description>Recent content on m4dfry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.m4dfry.space/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go WASM Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://blog.m4dfry.space/posts/go-wasm-benchmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.m4dfry.space/posts/go-wasm-benchmark/</guid>
      <description>In the last days I have often read articles on the recent Web Assembly (Wasm) support landed in Go 1.11 (expected in August &amp;hellip; soon). If it&amp;rsquo;s the first time you hear about web assembly I invite you to read this.
What was the first thing I thought to see its power ??
BENCHMARK obviously; let&amp;rsquo;s try the good old Fibonacci on WASM.
I implemented the function in the most optimized way I found and with some help I arrived at the following result:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://blog.m4dfry.space/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.m4dfry.space/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post, it is more a test than a real content, most likely I will be deleted when the real contents arrive.
In that case I salute you in advance
bb</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Me (But Were Afraid to Ask)</title>
      <link>https://blog.m4dfry.space/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.m4dfry.space/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Alessandro Sartori an italian full stack developer.
A fan of programming and electronics since my first studies.
I&amp;rsquo;m always looking for new technologies and I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by software automation and their use starting from home to industrial use.
I&amp;rsquo;m a supporter of android, linux and anything that allows me to get my hands under the hood.
I have a decent collection of Arduino, Raspberry and ARM microcontrollers that I&amp;rsquo;m very proud of, and recently I&amp;rsquo;m also playing with 3D printing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>